<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><?xml-stylesheet type="text/xml" href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xslt.xml"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><generator uri="http://jekyllrb.com" version="3.3.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2017-03-20T00:39:33-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000//</id><title type="html">The Captain’s Log</title><subtitle>Sometimes I come up with something insightful</subtitle><author><name>Captain Cornholio</name></author><entry><title type="html">Highs and Lows</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/highs-and-lows/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Highs and Lows" /><published>2017-03-19T10:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2017-03-19T10:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/highs-and-lows</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/highs-and-lows/">&lt;p&gt;One particular thing about writing is catering to your audience. Do you pretend you are writing to a new audience despite the fact that the people who read this most likely are familiar with you? Do I delve straight into specifics or do I have to give background about my life? Again, I hope to get that smoothed out over time, but for now I figure some background is necessary. Another thing, I will keep swear words to a minimum on here. Those are reserved for my Twitter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I began browsing Reddit during my senior year of high school around the fall of 2013. Back then, I was sucked into the default subreddits until I branched off into the niche subreddits about a year later. I proceeded to unsub from the defaults due to the frequency of reposts and non-sensical, unhelpful comment chains. Anyway, early on, one of the things that stuck with me was how many people believed that for everything good that happens to them, something bad was sure to follow. They were claiming that they never celebrate good things because they know something bad is around the corner and that they were happy when something bad happens because they know something good is coming up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I had never thought of it this way because life has its ups and downs. That is a given. If we only had ups, then it would not be challenging or fulfilling (maybe, I would not know). If we only had downs, that just blows. It is the balance that makes life exciting. Now, I am not a philosopher. I just wanted to tell about my day. The reason I brought that up is because if anything like that is true, it happened to me today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;the-good&quot;&gt;The Good&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am a NASCAR fan. I may delve into reasons why in a later post but we will assume I am quite emotionally invested in it. My favorite driver is Ryan Newman; my rationale being he won the first race I ever watched, the 2003 Banquet 400. After an anomalous 2003 in which Newman won eight races, he has solidified himself as a consistent driver who wins maybe once a year or so. Between then and 2013, his only winless seasons were 2006, 2007, and 2009. In 2013, he won the Brickyard 400 in July. I was a rising senior in high school chilling at Kennywood at the time and was unable to see the race live. I celebrated mainly because he had finally won at his home track. Little did I know, he would not win again until I was a spring semester junior in college.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Newman’s practice and qualifying times did not seem good all week, mid-teens at best, so when I was invited to play some pickup soccer, I gladly did that instead of watch the race. After soccer, I immediately had ultimate frisbee practice for two and a half hours. I checked the running order before practice began and Newman was running just outside the top-ten, nothing spectacular.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During a water break, I checked my phone and saw this notification.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;\assets\img\ryan_newman_won.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;OMG&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Was it a mistake? Was I seeing things? No way. Holy. Hell. Ryan Newman won a race. I freaked out and screamed to all my teammates. Their reactions ranged from incredulous to indifference, but two guys, guys from my year, actually celebrated and hugged me. I was amazed they cared. I was overjoyed. I was firing message after message to social media accounts, my parents, friends who cared about NASCAR, friends who did not care about NASCAR, people I barely knew, everyone. I missed the first half of a drill we were doing and the captains did not mind. For the first time in four years, I could say that my guy was a winner.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;the-bad-that-followed&quot;&gt;The Bad That Followed&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is also mid-March. That means March Madness. I am sure you can see where this is going. I am a member of two different bracket groups. One with high school friends for bragging rights and one with college friends for bragging rights &lt;em&gt;and&lt;/em&gt; with seventy dollars on the line. Seventy whole dollars. I could buy a Ryan Newman diecast to commemorate his epic win, one of the big ones, not the little, puny ones. My bracket had Duke winning so I was delighted when Villanova fell to Wisconsin yesterday. What I did not anticipate was Duke to have a meltdown of its own against the number seven seed of South Carolina. I watched in disbelief as my chosen team fell out of the tournament in the round of thirty-two as I was humiliated in the group chat along with another poor soul who had the unfortunate luck to put his faith in Duke to be champions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So now I have to wonder what is more humiliating, the fact I got rejected from Duke many years ago or the fact my coin flip bracket is now doing better than my actual bracket?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;\assets\img\coin_flip_bracket.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Uhhh... Go Gamecocks?&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;takeaways&quot;&gt;Takeaways&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I will reiterate that I do not believe that something good that happens to me will be immediately followed by something bad. Again, that is life and anyone can cherry pick good and bad things and claim they were indirectly caused by each other. Yet today, it definitely felt like that to me. Ryan Newman (who was at +8000 odds to win for my gambling literate friends), pulled of the improbable and won a race for the first time in four years. I was the happiest I had been in a long time. Two hours later, I was scribbling red all over my bracket as Duke, a team that many saw into the Final Four, a team that was a 6.5 point favorite, a team in which I was literally invested (hey, the ten dollar buy in could buy me two meals) let me down and lost in the second round. I have to admit I am not too happy at the moment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I guess the moral of the story is that I still have a lot of growing to do. It is probably not healthy to be so emotional about sports and things outside of your control. At the end of the day, it should be entertaining and relaxing. It is definitely possible to be passionate about something and not have your day ruined over it. As for now, I think it is time to order a new Ryan Newman diecast.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Captain Cornholio</name></author><summary type="html">One particular thing about writing is catering to your audience. Do you pretend you are writing to a new audience despite the fact that the people who read this most likely are familiar with you? Do I delve straight into specifics or do I have to give background about my life? Again, I hope to get that smoothed out over time, but for now I figure some background is necessary. Another thing, I will keep swear words to a minimum on here. Those are reserved for my Twitter.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Welcome to the Captain’s Log</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/welcome-to-the-captains-log/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Welcome to the Captain's Log" /><published>2017-03-18T10:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2017-03-18T10:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/welcome-to-the-captains-log</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/welcome-to-the-captains-log/">&lt;h1 id=&quot;greetings&quot;&gt;Greetings&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Greetings, I am Captain Cornholio. No, that is not my real name, but there is a story behind that. I have tossed around the idea of starting a blog for years now but was never motivated enough to do so. This past year, a couple friends and I discovered a blog being run by a friend from high school. This greatly influenced me to get up and running. In fact, I am using the same hosting service and a similar layout as his blog so credit goes out to him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now that is out of the way, let me introduce myself. I am &lt;a href=&quot;/about&quot;&gt;Captain Cornholio&lt;/a&gt;. It might be a pen name, a nickname, an alter-ego, or an indepedent entity. In any case, I am not entirely sure. For the purpose of this blog, we shall assume it is just a pen name.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;why-a-pen-name&quot;&gt;Why a pen name?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I used to be quite active on the Facebook, Twitter, and other forms of social media with my real name and was quite outspoken about certain topics. After awhile, I realized that the vast majority of “friends” and “followers” really did not care about my beliefs and posts and vice versa for the most part. This lead to the birth of the Captain. The Captain was developed in the winter of 2014 and was the face behind a private Twitter account that I only allowed my closest and trusted friends to follow. Inside the private Twitter, I would post musings, ideas, rants, and poorly taken pictures. There are many posts in there that should never be seen by the general public and I would risk my career if word of that got out. It has been three years, no calls, so I am fine on that end I suppose, but the Twitter has definitely calmed down over the years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So why did I choose Vault Boy as my mascot? I have no idea. I never even played Fallout. I rarely played video games that were not sports. There was just something about that wink and sly smile that drew me in. I hope I am not breaking any sort of copyright law (I probably am), but he has represented me well for the past three years. As for name itself, I am not sure where that came from. I guess it is one of those &lt;em&gt;random&lt;/em&gt; things high schoolers come up with. I am aware there is a character on Beavis and Butthead named the Great Cornholio, but I was not aware of that since I never watched the show.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is a level of anonymity I want to maintain when writing this blog, but that is made difficult because it limits what I can write about. Names, locations, and specific details will vary depending on what I deem appropriate to publish. This will probably adapt over time as I try to pinpoint who actually reads this (probably no more than five or ten people I have in mind) and figure out if something like this ever turns up in search engines. At some point, I would like to start posting pictures that may include myself and detailed stories that would allow my information to be found without much effort. As for now, I just want to see where this blog takes me. I do not know how committed to this I will be, but I hope for this to be a deeper analysis of my thoughts and observations that can not fit inside 140 characters on Twitter. Or it could just devolve into trash just like my Twitter. Only time will tell.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Captain Cornholio</name></author><summary type="html">Greetings</summary></entry></feed>
